http://www.magnaflow.com/pages/privacy-policy-2

We use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.
Icon / Play / Yellow
Created with Sketch.
Part
We do not have those parts for your vehicle. Please select another part category.
Next
Select Your Vehicle Specifications
It is possible we may not have parts for certain vehicles.
Part
We do not have those parts for your vehicle. Please select another part category.
Next
Where is your Vehicle Registered?
California
Converters in this catalog are based on Executive Orders issued by the California Air Resource Board and must be used in accordance with this information. In California, it is illegal to select a catalytic converter for installation based solely on vehicle weight and engine size. Learn more about the California Catalytic Converter law HERE.
Federal
All Federal catalytic converters meet EPA requirements. Federal Catalytic Converters are not legal for sale, installation or use in the state of California. Learn more about the Federal Catalytic Converter law HERE.
New York
All New York State & Maine Catalytic Converters are CARB and/or EPA compliant as applicable. Learn more about the New York and Maine Catalytic Converter law HERE.
Maine
All New York State & Maine Catalytic Converters are CARB and/or EPA compliant as applicable. Learn more about the New York and Maine Catalytic Converter law HERE.
Where is your Vehicle Registered?
California
Converters in this catalog are based on Executive Orders issued by the California Air Resource Board and must be used in accordance with this information. In California, it is illegal to select a catalytic converter for installation based solely on vehicle weight and engine size. Learn more about the California Catalytic Converter law HERE.
Federal
All Federal catalytic converters meet EPA requirements. Federal Catalytic Converters are not legal for sale, installation or use in the state of California. Learn more about the Federal Catalytic Converter law HERE.
New York
All New York State & Maine Catalytic Converters are CARB and/or EPA compliant as applicable. Learn more about the New York and Maine Catalytic Converter law HERE.
Maine
All New York State & Maine Catalytic Converters are CARB and/or EPA compliant as applicable. Learn more about the New York and Maine Catalytic Converter law HERE.
WHAT EMISSIONS STANDARD IS YOUR VEHICLE EQUIPPED WITH?
You can find out by inspecting the emissions sticker that is located in your engine compartment.
California
All 2001 model year and newer vehicles that were manufactured with California or 50-State emissions certification.
Federal EPA
All 2000 model year and earlier vehicles or any model year vehicle that was manufactured with EPA or Federal emissions non 50-State certification.
California
All 1993, 1994, 1996 and newer vehicles that were manufactured with California or 50-State emissions certification.
Federal EPA
All 1995 model year vehicles, and all 1992 model year or earlier vehicles. All model year vehicles that were manufactured with EPA or Federal emissions certification.
Vehicle Details
Select the option that best describes your vehicle. We want to make sure the part fits your specific vehicle so we need a little more information from you.
What is your EFN # ?
You can identify your vehicle’s EFN by checking your emission tag located under the hood, on the suspension tower or on the radiator shroud.
Next
Shop by Vehicle
Select your vehicle type to find the right parts for your vehicle.
Vehicle Specifications
Select your vehicle type to find the right parts for your vehicle.
Vehicle Specifications
Select your vehicle type to find the right parts for your vehicle.
Vehicle Registration
Select your vehicle type to find the right parts for your vehicle.
Vehicle Registration
Select your vehicle type to find the right parts for your vehicle.
Vehicle Emissions
Choose which emissions standard is equipped on your vehicle.
Vehicle Details
We need to know a little more about your vehicle.
Vehicle EFN
Choose which emissions standard is equipped on your vehicle.
PRIVACY POLICY
Car Sound Exhaust System, Inc., dba Magnaflow ("Magnaflow," "us," or "we") knows that you care how information about you is used and shared and respects the privacy of the visitors to the www.Magnaflow.com website (this "Site"). We have created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to demonstrate our commitment to privacy and security and supplement our Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by us when you use this Site, how the information will be used, how you can control the collection, when this Privacy Policy is effective, how we may change this Privacy Policy, and the steps we take to ensure that your personal information is protected. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
In this Privacy Policy, "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name (first and last), mailing address, email address, telephone number, billing information, etc.
All activities which you engage in on this Site are voluntary. You are not required to provide any personal information to us unless you choose to access features or services on the Site which require the information. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy or other Terms of Use posted on this Site, then you should immediately exit this Site, discontinue using the Site, and do not provide us with any personal information. By your use of this Site, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to our Terms of Use. The Terms of Use of this Site are expressly incorporated herein by reference and made a part of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through this Site and does not apply to any information we may collect from you at any place other than this Site.
Information We Collect
User-Provided Information: You may be required to provide personal information to access or use certain parts of our Site, or features of the Site or services, including without limitation, when you place an order, chat with a specialist, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, participate in any of our programs such as contests, sweepstakes or surveys, contact us with a comment, testimonial, question or complaint, etc. If you do not provide the requested personal information, you may not be able to access or use the features of the Site or service where such information is requested.
Depending upon the nature of the transaction, the personal information collected may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, fax number, date of birth, age, gender, credit card information, debit card information, Magnaflow part number and date of purchase, vehicle VIN number, vehicle license plate number and state, or other demographic information. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.
We may also collect personal information about you from other third parties, such as demographic firms, to make our future services and marketing efforts more efficient and personalized for you. We may combine all information we collect and may disclose this information within our corporate family of companies or our service providers.
Cookies Information: When you visit the Site, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Site. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Site or services may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our Site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses or other device identifiers, browser information, Internet Service Provider ("ISP"), operating system, location, date/time stamp, clickstream data, referring/exit pages and URLs, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.
Clear Gifs Information: When you use the Site or services, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personal information from your account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make this Site better for our users.
How We Use Your Information
We use the personal information you provide and any general information we receive from you to (a) operate, maintain, and provide to you the best possible features, products, functionality of the Site and experience; (b) analyze visits to the Site and learn about the interests of our visitors in aggregate and also on a personal level to better understand your interests and needs, so we can assess product demand and improve our products and services and deliver to you the type of content, features, products and promotions that you are most interested in; (c) process registration requests when you register for our programs or services, or otherwise administer your participation in our programs or services; (d) respond to your comments, questions or complaints and determine your satisfaction with our programs, products and services; (e) administer a promotion, contest, sweepstakes, survey or other Site feature; and (f) send you marketing communications and other information and materials you have chosen to receive regarding our products, services, marketing or special events. We also use your personal information for our everyday business purposes such as security, processing online orders, payment processing, analytics, operations, fraud detection and prevention, reporting, making back-ups and legal compliance.
Any personal information or content you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Site (for instance, any content you post) (referred to herein as "User Content") becomes available to the public via the Site and our business partners. User Content includes, but is not limited to, testimonials, reviews, comments, photos, videos, etc. If you remove User Content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content.
By providing Magnaflow your email address, you consent to our using the email address to send you Site and service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your email address to send you other messages including, but not limited to, newsletters, payment information, credit card update notifications, account status, legal updates, changes to features of the Site or services, product updates, special offers or promotions, or other account information. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by contacting us or clicking on the opt out link contained in the email message. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. You may not opt out of service-related emails.
Magnaflow may use certain information about you and/or your User Content without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Site is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing advertisements and promotions.
Magnaflow may develop special sites or administer promotions in cooperation with other companies. If you register at these "co-branded" sites or consent to receive email communications from our promotional partners, we may share your registration information (such as name and email address) with those companies.
Magnaflow reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the User Content you post on the Site. Magnaflow has the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason including, without limitation, if in its sole opinion, such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Use, or to protect or defend Magnaflow’s rights or property or those of any third party. Magnaflow also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party.
We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our Site and services; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (f) help you efficiently access information.
How We Share Your Information
Personally Identifiable Information: Magnaflow will not rent or sell your personal information to others. We may disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to those of our employees, contractors (including website operators), affiliated organizations, service providers, promotional partners and other third parties that provide support services to us or help us market our products and services, administer our programs and operations, fulfill your requests and orders, administer surveys, contests, and sweepstakes, or process any other information on our behalf to provide services available at our Site. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Magnaflow (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).
As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.
Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Magnaflow will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our Site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Magnaflow, our users or others.
We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our Site or services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful, as determined in our sole discretion. Release of your personal information for security purposes, as described in this agreement to any person or entity under any circumstances shall be based on a determination made solely by us, exercising our own discretion, permission for which is expressly granted by you to us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain services.
Magnaflow allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.
Magnaflow does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Magnaflow to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers.
How We Protect Your Information
Magnaflow uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Magnaflow or the Site and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Magnaflow makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. While we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online.
Compromise of Personal Information
In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Magnaflow will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.
Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Magnaflow does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on this Site. In the event we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us or email us at privacy@magnaflow.com.
Social Media Interactions
Magnaflow invites you to socialize and share your experiences with Magnaflow using Social Media tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, LinkedIn, YouTube, Google+ and Instagram. If you choose to use these tools, you may be sharing certain profile elements, including your comments. This sharing is subject to each social media program’s privacy policies. We also use Facebook Social Plugins to allow Facebook to share information and friends’ activities with its members while they are on our Site. For example, Social Plugins allow Facebook to show you your friends’ "Likes" on our product pages if you are logged into Facebook while using the services on our Site. Magnaflow does not receive or control any of the content from Facebook Social Plugins.
For more information about Facebook Social Plugins and other social media tools, click here.
We may allow you to sign in to your account using Facebook Connect. If you choose to do this, we may collect information necessary to facilitate social interactions such as friend lists, birthday, check-ins, basic profile information and your profile picture but only if the privacy settings you and your friends set within Facebook allow it. We will use the information we collect to create and facilitate an interactive social experience and to bring you products, services and programs from Magnaflow. Magnaflow will always comply with its Privacy Policy as well as with Facebook Connect terms regarding use of Facebook profile information.
Links to Other Websites
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site nor the information or content contained therein. Magnaflow may provide links to other websites to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of linked sites does not imply endorsement by Magnaflow of any of the linked sites. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our Site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. We do not ensure the security of your personal information if you visit websites not belonging to Magnaflow.
Notification Procedures
It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our Site page, as determined by Magnaflow in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes, modifications, additions, or deletions to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately on their posting to this Site. You should check this Privacy Policy periodically as its terms may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Site after we post any such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified policy and your agreement to abide and be bound by the modified policy. We will revise the "Last Updated" date found at the beginning of this Privacy Policy when we post changes to it.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, your dealings with this Site, or wish to update us with your preferences, you may contact us here or email privacy@magnaflow.com
IMPORTANT INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
Your California Privacy Rights
The information set forth herein is provided to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018.
The California Consumer Privacy Act provides our customers who are California residents the right to notice and disclosure of the collection of their personal information and the right to request that such information be deleted, as more fully set forth, commencing with Civil Code section 1798.100.
Consumer requests related to our Privacy Policy and compliance with California law can be submitted as follows:
By Mail to:Magnaflow California Privacy RightsAttention: Legal Department1901 Corporate Centre DriveOceanside, CA 92056.
By Email to:californiaprivacyrights@magnaflow.com
By Telephone:1-800-990-0905
For all requests, you must provide your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. You also need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response.
California Do Not Track Disclosures
California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how a website operator responds to "Do Not Track" (DNT) browser settings. DNT is a feature offered by some browsers which, when enabled, sends a signal to websites to request that your browsing is not tracked, such as by third party ad networks, social networks and analytic companies. Magnaflow does not currently take actions to respond to DNT signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a DNT standard once one is created. For information about DNT, please visit: www.allaboutdnt.org.
Last Updated: 12/30/19
How “Recycling For Refunds” Works Step 1: Purchase & Register Buy a new MagnaFlow Catalytic Converter and register your used OEM Catalytic Converter to recycle. Step 2: Shipping Send us your used OEM Catalytic Converter using our free shipping label. Step 3: Evaluation & Refund Once we receive and evaluate your OEM Catalytic Converter. Refunds will then be issued in the form of a MagnaFlow Visa® Prepaid Card up to $75. Step 4: Recycling Your job is done! You helped keep things clean and earned some green.
For additional program details, requirements and eligibility - learn more
How “Recycling For Refunds” Works Step 1: Purchase & Register Buy a new MagnaFlow Catalytic Converter and register your used OEM Catalytic Converter to recycle. Step 2: Shipping Send us your used OEM Catalytic Converter using our free shipping label. Step 3: Evaluation & Refund Once we receive and evaluate your OEM Catalytic Converter. Refunds will then be issued in the form of a MagnaFlow Visa® Prepaid Card up to $75. Step 4: Recycling Your job is done! You helped keep things clean and earned some green.
For additional program details, requirements and eligibility - learn more
How “Recycling For Refunds” Works Step 1: Purchase & Register Buy a new MagnaFlow Catalytic Converter and register your used OEM Catalytic Converter to recycle. Step 2: Shipping Send us your used OEM Catalytic Converter using our free shipping label. Step 3: Evaluation & Refund Once we receive and evaluate your OEM Catalytic Converter. Refunds will then be issued in the form of a MagnaFlow Visa® Prepaid Card up to $75. Step 4: Recycling Your job is done! You helped keep things clean and earned some green.
For additional program details, requirements and eligibility - learn more
Why we need this information MagnaFlow’s Recycling for Refunds program is subject to audit requiring us to maintain proof of the identity of the catalytic converter owner and the vehicle license and the VIN number of the vehicle that the catalytic converter was removed from.
For additional program details, requirements and eligibility - learn more
Why we need this information MagnaFlow’s Recycling for Refunds program is subject to audit requiring us to maintain proof of the identity of the catalytic converter owner and the vehicle license and the VIN number of the vehicle that the catalytic converter was removed from.
For additional program details, requirements and eligibility - learn more
Why we need this information MagnaFlow’s Recycling for Refunds program is subject to audit requiring us to maintain proof of the identity of the catalytic converter owner and the vehicle license and the VIN number of the vehicle that the catalytic converter was removed from.
For additional program details, requirements and eligibility - learn more
